♪The stars remember♪
♪النجوم تتذكر♪
♪The promise we made to each other♪
♪الوعد الذي قطعناه لبعضنا البعض♪
♪Every breeze carries your touch♪
♪كل نسيم يحمل لمستك♪
♪Kissing the warmth of my hand♪
♪تقبيل دفء يدي♪
♪So no matter how far it may be, don't hesitate♪
♪لذا مهما كان الأمر بعيدًا، فلا تتردد♪
♪Love will guide us through♪
♪الحب سوف يرشدنا خلال♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would I have met you a little sooner?♪
♪هل كنت سألتقي بك في وقت أقرب؟♪
♪Like night embracing the fireworks' glow♪
♪مثل الليل يحتضن توهج الألعاب النارية♪
♪You and I were meant to hold hands♪
♪لقد كان من المفترض أن نمسك أيدي بعضنا البعض♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would destiny have brought us together?♪
♪هل كان القدر سيجمعنا معًا؟♪
♪Turning thorns into silver threads on a crown♪
♪تحويل الأشواك إلى خيوط فضية على التاج♪
♪I'll weave them for you, forever around♪
♪سأنسجها لك، إلى الأبد حولك♪
=Long Planned Love=
=الحب المخطط له منذ فترة طويلة=
=Episode 4=
=الحلقة 4=
Jiang Yawei is just too much.
جيانج ياوي هو أكثر من اللازم.
She actually pushed Cheng off
لقد دفعت تشنغ بعيدا في الواقع
from such a high place.
من هذا المكان المرتفع.
How is she doing now?
كيف حالها الآن؟
She hasn't woken up.
لم تستيقظ بعد.
When will you and Zhou Tingyan get here?
متى ستصل أنت وتشو تينغيان إلى هنا؟
Almost there.
تقريبا هناك.
Meng Tang.
منغ تانغ.
Is Jian Cheng doing okay?
هل جيان تشنغ بخير؟
You're not welcome.
أنت غير مرحب بك.
Get out.
اخرج.
Meng Tang.
منغ تانغ.
I just came to check on her.
لقد جئت فقط للتحقق منها.
How is Jian Cheng?
كيف حال جيان تشنغ؟
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
I feel responsible.
أشعر بالمسؤولية.
It was you who pushed her down.
لقد كنت أنت الذي دفعها إلى الأسفل.
Then you jumped down yourself.
ثم قفزت إلى الأسفل بنفسك.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
It is...
إنها...
I did have her called out to meet me.
لقد طلبت منها أن تلتقي بي.
But once I saw her,
ولكن بمجرد أن رأيتها،
I only begged her.
لقد توسلت لها فقط.
I wanted her to show mercy and let me go.
أردت منها أن تظهر الرحمة وتسمح لي بالذهاب.
She refused.
لقد رفضت.
She even grabbed my chin
حتى أنها أمسكت بذقني
and threatened me.
وهددني.
Told me to break up with Yufeng.
طلب مني أن أنهي علاقتي مع يوفينغ.
She got more and more worked up,
لقد أصبحت أكثر وأكثر انزعاجا،
then accidentally pushed me.
ثم دفعني عن طريق الخطأ.
Jiang Yawei.
جيانغ ياوي.
I don't believe every single word you say.
لا أصدق كل كلمة تقولها.
You better hope Cheng's fine.
من الأفضل أن تأمل أن يكون تشنغ بخير.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
you'll face consequences.
سوف تواجه العواقب.
I'm not lying.
أنا لا أكذب.
Everything I said is true.
كل ما قلته صحيح.
I wronged Jian Cheng.
لقد ظلمت جيان تشنغ.
She pushed me down the stairs, but I don't blame her.
لقد دفعتني إلى أسفل الدرج، ولكنني لا ألومها.
I just want to make sure she's okay.
أريد فقط التأكد من أنها بخير.
Meng Tang.
منغ تانغ.
Yawei came here
ياوي جاء هنا
because she's kind-hearted.
لأنها طيبة القلب.
What Jian Cheng did to her is against the law.
ما فعله جيان تشنغ لها هو مخالف للقانون.
Are you serious?
هل انت جاد؟
Yufeng, has your brain stopped working?
يوفينغ، هل توقف عقلك عن العمل؟
There is no CCTV.
لا يوجد كاميرات مراقبة.
Whatever Yawei says, you just believe it?
مهما قال ياوي، هل تصدقه فقط؟
You and Cheng grew up together.
لقد نشأت أنت وتشنغ معًا.
Don't you know what kind of person she is?
ألا تعرف أي نوع من الأشخاص هي؟
You rather trust a homewrecker?
هل تفضل أن تثق في شخص يدمر المنزل؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Yufeng, touch her again and see what happens.
يوفينغ، لمسها مرة أخرى وانظر ماذا سيحدث.
I'm okay.
انا بخير.
Uncle Zhou.
العم تشو.
The doctor said Jian Cheng needs rest.
قال الطبيب أن جيان تشنغ يحتاج إلى الراحة.
Take your girl and get out.
خذ فتاتك واخرج.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Cheng, you're awake.
تشنغ، أنت مستيقظ.
Zhou.
تشو.
Zhou Tingyan.
تشو تينغيان.
Uncle Zhou.
العم تشو.
Give me a hug.
أعطني عناق.
(She's using Uncle Zhou like a helper.)
(إنها تستخدم العم تشو كمساعد.)
(Got some nerve.)
(حصلت على بعض الشجاعة.)
(This is bad.)
(هذا سيء.)
(Cheng must have)
(يجب أن يكون لدى تشنغ)
(messed up her head.)
(أفسدت رأسها.)
Is your head hurting?
هل رأسك يؤلمك؟
I'll go get the doctor.
سأذهب لإحضار الطبيب.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
My head's fine.
رأسي بخير.
Honey.
عسل.
This…
هذا…
Yesterday,
أمس،
when I fell down,
عندما سقطت،
I was scared to death.
لقد كنت خائفة حتى الموت.
I thought I'd never see you again.
اعتقدت أنني لن أراك مرة أخرى.
Cheng.
تشنغ.
Maybe sleep a bit more?
ربما النوم أكثر قليلا؟
Jian Cheng.
جيان تشنغ.
You're playing dumb.
أنت تلعب بالغباء.
What trick is it this time?
ما هي الخدعة هذه المرة؟
You really think
هل تعتقد حقا
this is getting under my skin?
هل هذا الأمر يضايقني؟
You called me honey.
لقد ناديتني بالعسل.
Does that mean we're married?
هل هذا يعني أننا متزوجين؟
No, we're not.
لا، نحن لسنا كذلك.
But we are engaged.
ولكننا منخرطون.
After New Year,
بعد العام الجديد،
we'll be getting married.
سوف نتزوج.
Why are you asking me such weird questions?
لماذا تسألني مثل هذه الأسئلة الغريبة؟
Is this... memory loss?
هل هذا... فقدان الذاكرة؟
Looks like a blessing in disguise.
يبدو وكأنه نعمة مقنعة.
Jian Cheng.
جيان تشنغ.
Stop pretending.
توقف عن التظاهر.
You asked me to call off the engagement.
لقد طلبت مني إلغاء الخطوبة.
So what is this act now?
فما هو هذا الفعل الآن؟
Uncle Zhou.
العم تشو.
She's using you just to get at me.
إنها تستخدمك فقط للوصول إلي.
Enough.
كافٍ.
You hit your head on the fall.
لقد ضربت رأسك في السقوط.
Get the doctor to check.
اطلب من الطبيب أن يفحصك.
All tests came back normal.
جميع الاختبارات جاءت طبيعية.
She just needs rest.
إنها تحتاج فقط إلى الراحة.
As for the memory confusion,
أما بالنسبة لارتباك الذاكرة،
it might just be temporary.
ربما يكون هذا مؤقتًا فقط.
Don't worry, it won't affect daily life.
لا تقلق، لن يؤثر ذلك على حياتك اليومية.
Doctor.
طبيب.
She's pretending, right?
إنها تتظاهر، أليس كذلك؟
How could such a thing even happen?
كيف يمكن أن يحدث مثل هذا الشيء؟
Beyond ridiculous.
أكثر من سخيف.
Jian Cheng, get up.
جيان تشنغ، استيقظ.
Drop the act.
أسقط الفعل.
Leave.
يترك.
She just woke up and needs peace.
لقد استيقظت للتو وتحتاج إلى السلام.
(Jian Cheng,)
(جيان تشنغ،)
(let's see how long you can keep this up.)
(دعونا نرى إلى متى يمكنك الاستمرار على هذا المنوال.)
Let's head back.
دعونا نعود إلى الوراء.
Come on.
تعال.
Cheng.
تشنغ.
Get some proper rest first.
احصل على قسط مناسب من الراحة أولاً.
Mm.
مم.
I'll check with the doctor.
سأتحقق مع الطبيب.
Be back in a bit.
سأعود بعد قليل.
I hit my head pretty hard.
لقد ضربت رأسي بقوة.
You look pretty happy.
تبدو سعيداً جداً.
Of course, I'm happy.
بالطبع أنا سعيد.
You forgot about that jerk Zhou Yufeng.
لقد نسيت ذلك الأحمق تشو يوفينغ.
That's worth a bottle of wine to celebrate.
إنه يستحق زجاجة من النبيذ للاحتفال.
I didn't forget.
لم أنسى.
You didn't?
لم تفعل؟
Then what was that just now?
ثم ماذا كان ذلك للتو؟
I was acting.
كنت امثل.
Come on.
تعال.
What's going on between you and Jiang Yawei?
ماذا يحدث بينك وبين جيانج ياوي؟
She jumped on her own.
لقد قفزت من تلقاء نفسها.
Knew it.
عرفت ذلك.
Definitely one of her dirty tricks.
بالتأكيد واحدة من حيلها القذرة.
That way she doesn't have to apologize
بهذه الطريقة لن تضطر إلى الاعتذار
and can throw the blame on you.
ويمكن أن يلقي اللوم عليك.
That's just too much.
هذا كثير جدًا.
I'll go find her.
سأذهب للبحث عنها.
Don't go.
لا تذهب.
- Let her be. - Seriously?
- دعها تكون. - بجدية؟
She's trying to ruin your reputation.
إنها تحاول تدمير سمعتك.
You owe this one to Qin Zhuo and Zhou Tingyan.
أنت مدين بهذا إلى تشين تشو وتشو تينغيان.
Tingyan saw Jiang Yawei lying next to you.
رأى تينغيان جيانغ ياوي مستلقيًا بجانبك.
He instantly told Qin Zhuo
أخبر تشين تشو على الفور
to keep it under wraps.
لإبقائه طي الكتمان.
Otherwise, who knows what rumors would spread.
وإلا فمن يدري ما هي الشائعات التي ستنتشر.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
you just focus on resting now.
ركز فقط على الراحة الآن.
Don't worry about a thing.
لا تقلق بشأن أي شيء.
(Jian Wenqian) (Jian Cheng)
(جيان وينكيان) (جيان تشنغ)
(is playing dumb.)
(يلعب دور الغبي.)
(And Zhou Tingyan sealed off the news.)
(وختم تشو تينغيان الخبر.)
(Last night's act was all for nothing.)
(كان كل ما حدث الليلة الماضية بلا فائدة.)
(Jian Wenqian)
(جيان ون تشيان)
How did it go?
كيف كان الأمر؟
Cheng said
قال تشنغ
she missed a step and fell on her own.
لقد أخطأت خطوة وسقطت بمفردها.
But I don't buy it.
ولكنني لا أصدق ذلك.
Jiang Yawei.
جيانغ ياوي.
You should be grateful.
ينبغي عليك أن تكون شاكرا.
Cheng doesn't remember all of you.
تشنغ لا يتذكركم جميعا.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
if you try any more dirty tricks,
إذا حاولت أي حيل قذرة أخرى،
I'll crush your dream of joining the wealthy elite.
سأحطم حلمك بالانضمام إلى النخبة الثرية.
- I... - I heard everything.
- أنا... - سمعت كل شيء.
I'll take care of the rest.
سأعتني بالباقي.
Hey, Qin Zhuo.
مهلا، تشين تشو.
Cheng wants to keep the peace.
تشنغ يريد الحفاظ على السلام.
She said she fell down on her own.
قالت أنها سقطت من تلقاء نفسها.
Maybe we should just let it go.
ربما يجب علينا أن نترك الأمر يمر.
So she won't get upset later
حتى لا تنزعج لاحقًا
and start an argument with them.
وبدء الجدال معهم.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Looks like
يبدو مثل
Jian Cheng is determined
جيان تشنغ مصمم
to cut all ties with Zhou Yufeng.
قطع جميع العلاقات مع تشو يوفينغ.
Meng Tang is passing on Cheng's message.
منغ تانغ ينقل رسالة تشنغ.
Cheng can do
تشنغ يمكنه أن يفعل
whatever she wants.
كل ما تريد.
But Little Princess seems stuck on you.
لكن يبدو أن الأميرة الصغيرة عالقة فيك.
What do you plan to do?
ماذا تخطط أن تفعل؟
I gave her the chance
لقد أعطيتها الفرصة
and made her cling to me.
وجعلتها تلتصق بي.
What?
ماذا؟
I'm going to marry her.
سأتزوجها.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
(Today's Trending)
(الاتجاهات اليوم)
(It really didn't make the trending.)
(لم يكن في الواقع رائجًا.)
(Zhou Tingyan's crisis control is impressive.)
(إن سيطرة تشو تينغيان على الأزمة مثيرة للإعجاب.)
Honey.
عسل.
The doctor already told me.
لقد أخبرني الطبيب بالفعل.
(No way.)
(مستحيل.)
(How could I be exposed this fast?)
(كيف يمكن أن أتعرض للخطر بهذه السرعة؟)
(Oh my gosh.)
(يا إلهي.)
(Please let me find a hole to hide in.)
(أرجوك دعني أجد حفرة للاختباء فيها.)
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would I have met you a little sooner?♪
♪هل كنت سألتقي بك في وقت أقرب؟♪
A concussion doesn't
الارتجاج لا
affect us getting married.
يؤثر علينا الزواج.
♪You and I were meant to hold hands♪
♪لقد كان من المفترض أن نمسك أيدي بعضنا البعض♪
Good to hear.
يسعدني سماع ذلك.
♪Like fate answering all my prayers♪
♪مثل القدر الذي يجيب على كل صلواتي♪
♪You lower your head to crown me♪
♪تخفض رأسك لتتوجني♪
♪Rumors forged into fragments of the crown♪
♪الشائعات المزورة في شظايا التاج♪
♪Maybe this story is just too classic♪
♪ربما تكون هذه القصة كلاسيكية للغاية♪
♪In the abyss, a garden was sown and remembered♪
♪في الهاوية، زرعت حديقة وتذكرت♪
♪In the ruins, you raise the moon, though broken♪
♪في الأنقاض، ترفع القمر، رغم أنه مكسور♪
♪I see the prophecy at dawn♪
♪أرى النبوءة عند الفجر♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would I have met you a little sooner?♪
♪هل كنت سألتقي بك في وقت أقرب؟♪
♪Like night embracing the fireworks' glow♪
♪مثل الليل يحتضن توهج الألعاب النارية♪
♪You and I were meant to hold hands♪
♪لقد كان من المفترض أن نمسك أيدي بعضنا البعض♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would destiny have brought us together?♪
♪هل كان القدر سيجمعنا معًا؟♪
♪Turning thorns into silver threads on a crown♪
♪تحويل الأشواك إلى خيوط فضية على التاج♪
♪I'll weave them for you, forever around♪
♪سأنسجها لك، إلى الأبد حولك♪
♪In your eyes, I see twinkling starlight♪
♪في عينيك، أرى ضوء النجوم المتلألئ♪
♪That's why I dare to face the whole world♪
♪لهذا السبب أجرؤ على مواجهة العالم أجمع♪
♪Even the universe♪
♪حتى الكون♪
♪Tacitly approves of the romantic vow♪
♪يوافق ضمنيًا على العهد الرومانسي♪
♪Our love is the optimal solution♪
♪حبنا هو الحل الأمثل♪
♪The stars remember♪
♪النجوم تتذكر♪
♪The promise we made to each other♪
♪الوعد الذي قطعناه لبعضنا البعض♪
♪Every breeze carries your touch♪
♪كل نسيم يحمل لمستك♪
♪Kissing the warmth of my hand♪
♪تقبيل دفء يدي♪
♪So no matter how far it may be, don't hesitate♪
♪لذا مهما كان الأمر بعيدًا، فلا تتردد♪